Maltese, Serphin R.; Papers apap382
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Senate Subject Files, 1965-2009; 22.7 cubic ft.
  - Franklin K. Lane High School, 1996-1998; 2000; Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Grover Cleveland School, 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Public School 60, 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Political Newspapers, 1996; 2008 (Oversize 1, Folder 20)
  - Maltese - Roseanne Rosado and Ann Michitsch, 1997 February 11 (Video-tape 27)
  - Administrative Files, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Buena Vida Nursing Home, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Community Events, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Financial Disclosure Statement, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Friends of Rudy Giuliani, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Holy Child Jesus School, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Italy Trips, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Pamphlets, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Parent - Teacher Association, Public School 229, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Public School 97, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Reports, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Serphin Maltese Prime Sponsor Legislation, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Women's History Month, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Higher Education, 1997; Undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Queens County Republican Party Rudy Giuliani Petition, 1997; Undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Ridgewood Senior Citizens Center Bylaws etc., 1997; Undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - St. John's University, 1997; Undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Anne Paolucci, CUNY, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - The Committee for Better Transit, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Community Advocacy Center, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Hunter College, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Italian and Jewish Americans, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Lehman College Art Gallery, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Queens College, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Queens High School Superintendent, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - 1998 Election, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Martin Luther High School, 1997-1998; 2000 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1997-1998; 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Junior High School 210, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - N.Y.C Department of Environmental Protection, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Christ the King Regional High School, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - School Lists, 1997; 1999; Undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Tom Ognibene, 1997; 1999; Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - N.Y.C. Coalition for Fairness to Veterans, 1997; 2000 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Public School 90, 1997; 2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - The Board of Directors of the American Conservative Union, 1997-2001 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Administrative Files, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Airport Bill, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Anne Paolucci, CUNY Board of Trustees, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - "Bride of Finkelstein: A Titanic Disaster" Seating Chart, 1998 (Oversize 1, Folder 21)
  - Clippings (1 of 5), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Clippings (2 of 5), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Clippings (3 of 5), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Clippings (4 of 5), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Clippings (5 of 5), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1998 (Oversize 1, Folder 23)
  - Community Events (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Community Events (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Dexter Park, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Greater Jamaica Development Corp. Port Authority, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - John Valverde Clemency Application (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - John Valverde Clemency Application (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Pamphlets, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Photographs Logs, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Public School 71, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Reports, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Ridgewood Intermediate School No. 93, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Serph's Birthday and Boss Day Celebration, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Steve Forbes Photographs, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Voter's Directory, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 75th Street Block Association, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Little Dolphin School, 1998; Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - City University of New York, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Scholarships for College, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Senior Centers Dept. of Aging, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Queens College and CUNY, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Lodico, Diego, 1998-1999; 2003-2006; 2009; Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Abortion Funding through Medicaid, 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - A.S.P.C.A and Animal Rights, 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - New York City Parent Organizing Consortium, 1998-2000; Undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Congratulations Letters Regarding Election Wins, 1998; 2000 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - New York State Conservative Party, 1998; 2000; Undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Con Edison, 1998; 2001 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - YMCA, 1998; 2001 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Maltese - 30:00 Triangle Shirtwaist Factory, 1999 March 31 (Video-tape 28)
  - Administrative Files, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Anne A. Paolucci Resignation, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Clippings (1 of 3), 1999 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Clippings (2 of 3), 1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Clippings (3 of 3), 1999 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Community Events, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Constituent Surveys, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (1 of 6), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (2 of 6), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (3 of 6), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (4 of 6), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (5 of 6), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (6 of 6), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Intermediate School 66, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Junior High School 73, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Moldoff, William M., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlets, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Reports, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - The New York Hall of Science, 1999; Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Airport Privatization, BAA, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Senate Finance, 1999; 2001 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Queens Public Television, 1999; 2001 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Opening Conference - International Conference Center - Anne and Henry Paolucci, 2000 March 25 (Video-tape 29)
  - Administrative Files, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Board of Elections, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Community Events, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Korean War Event Flyer, 2000 (Oversize 1, Folder 24)
  - Newsletters, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Wyckoff - Snedicver Family Cemetery, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Abandoned Infant Protection Act, 2000; Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - An Artist's Journey, 2000; Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Republican National Convention, 2000; Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Capital Projects, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Community Board No. 9 and St. Anthony's Property, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Report for Civic and Community Leaders, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Unborn Victims of Violence Act, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Maltese and Constance Maltese, 15:00, 2001 March 15 (Video-tape 30)
  - Serf's Up - Senator Serphin Maltese Hawaiian Luau CD-ROM, 2001 August 29 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Maltese, 15:00 - Lisa Rosen, 2001 September 4 (Video-tape 31)
  - Inside Albany - Gender Neural Constitution, Election 2001, School Aid, Electricity Market Price, 2001 November 2 (Video-tape 32)
  - Administrative Files, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Bloomberg, Michael, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Cease and Desist Law, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Christ the King, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Citizens Union Voters Directory, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Community Events, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Direct Mailings, Pamphlets and Flyers, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Event Programs, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Event Programs, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Freedom Alert, 2001 (Oversize 1, Folder 25)
  - Goodman Ray, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Greater Ridgewood Youth Council, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Haggerty, John and the 3 Boys, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Inauguration, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Italian Membership Organizations, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Memos, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Mulrow, Bill - Comptroller, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - National Arts Club, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - New York State Catholic Conference, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - New York Hall of Science, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - News Releases, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Newsletters, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - O'Neil Charles, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Order Sons of Italy in America, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Paolucci, Anne, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Reapportionment - 15th Senate District, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Political Events, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Public Disclosure Report, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Purple Heart Stamp, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Queens Newspapers - 9/11, 2001 (Oversize 1, Folder 26)
  - Reports, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Savarese, Paul, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - "The Senator vs. The Sopranos," Queens Courier, 2001 (Oversize 1, Folder 27)
  - September 11th, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Slagus, Al - Memos, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - "The Sopranos" Protest, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Stabile, Alfonso, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Stuyvesant High School, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Term Limits, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Veterans, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Crowley, Elizabeth, 2001; Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Del Vecchio, Constance Maltese, 2001; Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Ognibene, Tom, 2001; Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - United Council for Veterans' Rights, 2001; Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Wycoff Heights Medical Center, 2001; 2003 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Tan, Meilin, 2001; 2005; Undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Admiral Ave Site Development, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Board of Education, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Community School Board 27, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Legislation, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Italian Charities of America, 2001-2003 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Triangle Fire, 2001-2004 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Queens Theatre in the Park Legislative Revue 2002, 2002 November 23 (Video-tape 33)
  - Administrative Files, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Bios, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Bloomberg Judicial Panel, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Board of Elections, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Campaign Materials, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Clippings (1 of 3), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Clippings (2 of 3), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Clippings (3 of 3), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Community Events, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Constituents Lost on 9/11, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Community Board 5, Land use Committee, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 2002 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Criminal Procedure and Temporary Release Laws, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Direct Mailers, Pamphlets, and Flyers, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Election Results, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Endorsements, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Event Programs, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Family Defense Council, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Italian American Civil Rights, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Italian American Museum, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Italian-American State Legislators, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Union, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Contains sensitive materials
  - Johnson Stuart, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Juniper Berry, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Kiwanis Club of Glendale, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - League of Women Voters, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Mayoral Recommendations, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Maltese Web Page, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Memos, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Negatives, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - New York Republican State Committee, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - New York State Senate Majority, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - New York State Senate Republican Campaign Committee, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Newsletters, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - News Releases, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Pataki, George, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Photos, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Political Events, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - PoliticsNY.com - Throop's Scoop, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Publications, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - PS 147, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Queens County District Attorney, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Queens County Republican Committee vs Board of Elections, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Queen's County Republican Party, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Reports (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Reports (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Scafidi, Andrew, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Senate Judiciary Committee, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Senate Majority Initiative Forms, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Senate Memos, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Senate Proclamations, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Shield Law, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Sportsman's Association for Firearm Education, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Stuyvesant High School, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Veterans, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Veteran's Day Parade - Photo, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Voter's Directory, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Women of Distinction, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Woodhaven Residents' Block Association, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Community Capital Assistance Program (CCAP), 2002; Undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Designating Petitions, 2002; Undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Birthday Letters, 2002; 2004 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - 104 Precinct, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Bella Italia Mia, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Christ the King High School, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Firehouse Closures, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Greater Woodhaven Development Corporation, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Judges, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Vietnam Veterans of America, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Del Vecchio Maltese, Constance, 2002-2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Maltese-15:00, 2003 January 14 (Video-tape 34)
  - Senate Resolution Honoring Ronan Tynan, 2003 March 10 (Video-tape 35)
  - Maltese with Victor LaMagne, Historian Post 1172 - 15:00, 2003 June 12 (Video-tape 36)
  - 28th Assembly District Race, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Adequate Shelter for Dugs, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Files, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - American Conservative Union, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - American Red Cross, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Archbishop Molloy High School, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Bloomberg, Mike, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Cardella Center, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Charter Revision Commission - NYC, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - City Council, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Clippings (1 of 4), 2003 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Clippings (2 of 4), 2003 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Clippings (3 of 4), 2003 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Clippings (4 of 4), 2003 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Closure of Engine Company 293, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Community Events (1 of 7), 2003 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Community Events (2 of 7), 2003 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Community Events (3 of 7), 2003 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Community Events (4 of 7), 2003 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Community Events (5 of 7), 2003 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Community Events (6 of 7), 2003 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Community Events (7 of 7), 2003 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Conservative Publications, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Coward, Kathryn, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Destiny USA, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Direct Mailings, Pamphlets, and Flyers, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Election Day, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Fabrizi, Marie - Queen's Board of Elections, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Gateway National Recreation Area, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Greater Ridgewood Youth Council, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Hope, Bob, Resolution, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Immigration, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Italian American State Legislators, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Italians Organizations, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Keene, David, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Days, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Legislative Questionnaire, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Legislative Program, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Madonia Meeting Memo, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Maltese Legislation, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Mayor's Judiciary, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - McCarthyism, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Medicaid Funding - Abortions, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Mullen, Cassandra, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - New York City Parks and Recreations, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - New York State Boating Regulations, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Newsletters, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - News Releases, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Padavan, Senator Frank, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Pataki, George, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Patriot Act, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Photos, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Political Events, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Queensborough Community College, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Queens Council on The Arts, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Rally to Support Our Troops, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Rally to Support Our Troops News Clippings, 2003 (Oversize 1, Folder 29)
  - Rent Laws, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Reports, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Republican Committees, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Senate Legislative Package to Support Out Troops, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Senate Memoranda, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Skyscraper Safety Campaign, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Senate Resolution Calendar, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Senate Selected Record Screen, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Sengupta Uma, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Van Cortlandt Park Alienation, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - State Budget, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Susan B. Anthony List, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Programs, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Board of Education, 2003; Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Jewish War Veterans, 2003; Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Katz, Melinda, 2003; Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Keyspan, 2003; Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Sikhs, 2003; Undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Stewart, Lynne F. -Freedom of Speech, 2003; Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Certificates of Appreciation, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Community Board No.5, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Gay Marriage, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Report for Civic and Community Leaders, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - New York City Council State Legislative Agenda, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Senator Maltese with Senator Morahan - Help American Vote Act, 2004 May 19 (Video-tape 37)
  - American Conservative Union, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Armenian Committee Proclamation, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Bush/Cheney Campaign, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Business Leaders of Tomorrow, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Campaign Materials, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Child Online Protection Act (COPA), 2004 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Clippings (1 of 3), 2004 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Clippings (2 of 3), 2004 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Clippings (3 of 3), 2004 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Community Events, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Conservative Political Action Conference, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Council of Catholic Women, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Cross Harbor Freight Project, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Death Penalty, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Delegates by Congressional District, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - De Sapio Carmine, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Detl, Bo - Proclamations for 9/11 Security Guards, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Direct Mailers, Pamphlets,, and Flyers, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Dixon Place, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Education Department - NYC Regions, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Election Figures, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Election Law Cases, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - General Slocum Memorial, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Glendale Yeshiva, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Graduate Certificate Request Letters, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Italian American Legal Defense, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Italian Charities, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Italian Organizations, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Judges, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Kiwanis Awards, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Klein Farm, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Labaschi, Anthony, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - LaGuardia Community College, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Maltese Bills, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Mayor Biographies, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - MTA Takeover, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Monahan Fund, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - New York Republican State Committee, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - New York State Assembly Citation, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Newsletters, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - News Releases, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Nursing Home and Long Term Care Issues, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Paolucci, Anne, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Political Events, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Pruszynski, Stanley, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Quattrocchi, Fabrizio, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Queens Library, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Regan Resolution, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Republican National Convention, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Senate Correspondence, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Senate Memoranda, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Shaw, Steve - Mayoral Campaign, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Tribute to Ronald Reagan, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Right to Life Committee, 2004; Undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Defense of Marriage Act, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Ognibene, Thomas, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Triangle, 2004-2006; Undated (Box 19, Folder 13)